Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum C
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Consolidated General File, Series III
  - P - Philippines
    - Silliman University
      - Rich, Victor and Jeanne (Visiting Professor0, 1988-1992 (Box 25, Folder 837)
      - Tiempo, Eldiberto K., 1981-1988 (Box 25, Folder 838)
      - Tiempo, Edith L., 1980-1993 (Box 25, Folder 839)
      - Udarbe, Procesou, 1980-1986 (Box 25, Folder 840)
      - Vande Vusse, Frederick, 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 841)
      - Project evaluation reports, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 842-843)
    - Southern Christian College
      - Board meeting, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 844)
      - Information questionnaire (Box 25, Folder 845)
      - Mapanao, Eliezer D., 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 846-847)
      - Proposals and grants, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 848-850)
      - Ten-year development plan (Box 25, Folder 851)
    - Trinity College
      - General correspondence (Box 26, Folder 852)
      - Proposals and grants, 1980-1987 (Box 26, Folder 853-857)
      - Guerrero, Arturo, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 858)
      - Information questionnaire (Box 26, Folder 859)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 860)
    - Xavier University
      - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 861)
      - Information questionnaire (Box 26, Folder 862)
      - Overseas personnel (Box 26, Folder 863)
      - Proposals and grants, 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 864-865)
    - Union Christian College
      - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 866)
    - Union Theological Seminairy, Dasmarinas
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 867)
  - Q - General
    - Q (Box 26, Folder 868)
    - Queens College, Charlotte, NC, 1980-1987 (Box 26, Folder 869)
  - R - General
    - Ra - Re (Box 26, Folder 870)
    - Ri - Ry (Box 26, Folder 871)
    - Ravenholt, Mr. and Mrs. Albert, 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 872)
    - Regional Institute of Higher Education and Development, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 873)
    - Regional News Service (Box 26, Folder 874)
    - Rempel, Herbert and Sarah, 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 875)
    - Rich, Andrew F. and Sally E., 1983-1987 (Box 26, Folder 876)
    - Roberts, Nanette M. (United Church Board for Homeland Ministries), 1982-1988 (Box 26, Folder 877)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box 26, Folder 878)
    - Rockland Community College (Box 26, Folder 879)
    - Rogers, Frances V. V. (estate of), 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 880)
    - Roger Williams College (Box 26, Folder 881)
    - Rohlfs, Mrs. Marcus (Ruth), 1980-1987 (Box 26, Folder 882)
    - Rork, John B., 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 883)
    - Ross, Donald F. and Jeanne F. Martin, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 884)
    - Rothfork, John (New Mexico Institute of Mining and Technology) (Box 26, Folder 885)
    - Rottsolk, Katherine M., see Petersen, Mrs. Arnold J.
  - S - General
    - Sh - Sm (Box 26, Folder 887)
    - So - St (Box 26, Folder 888)
    - Su - Sz (Box 26, Folder 889)
    - St. Olaf College, 1980-1987 (Box 26, Folder 890)
    - Salonga, Jovito, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 891)
    - Sandsberry, Lynne E., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 892)
    - Santos, Ester Abellera, 1980-1987 (Box 26, Folder 893)
    - Saratoga Federated Church, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 894)
    - Satneck, Walter J., 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 895)
    - Sawin, Margaret M., 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 896)
    - Schechter, Dr. and Mrs. William (Zelma), 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 897)
    - Schmidt, Dr. and Mrs. William J. (Jean E.), 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 898)
    - Scott, Mrs. Roderick (Agnes K.), 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 899)
    - Seals, identification symbols - various universities and colleges (Box 27, Folder 900)
    - Semke, Dr. and Mrs. Charles (Harriet), 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 901)
    - Shields, Richard O (Box 27, Folder 902)
    - Singh, Ram - writings, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1375)
    - Skillingstad, S. J., Rev. P. Delmar, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 903)
    - Smith, Rev. and Mrs. Harold W. (Camilla), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 904)
    - Smith, Robert V. and Joyce Irwin, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 905)
    - Smock, Audrey C., 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 906)
    - Sohl, Joyce D. (Box 27, Folder 907)
    - Sri Lanka - general correspondence (Box 27, Folder 908)
    - Stemper, William H. Jr. (Forum for Corporate Responsibility), 1982-1986 (Box 27, Folder 909)
    - Stine, Esther C (Box 27, Folder 910)
    - Sue, Ed (architect for Payap College Chapel), 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 911)
    - Sunlife of Canada, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 912)
    - Svercel, Mrs. and Mrs. Charles J., 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 913)
    - Swan, Dr. and Mrs. Frederick R. (Patricia), 1981-1987 (Box 27, Folder 914)
    - Swatek, Edwin Paul, Jr., 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 915)
    - Swendseid, M. Douglas, 1980-1988 (Box 27, Folder 916)
    - Swinney, Dr. and Mrs. Harry, 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 917)
  - T - General
    - T (Box 27, Folder 918)
    - Tan, Margaret Hee-Leng (pianist), 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 919)
    - Tang, Mr. and Mrs. Lung-Yin, 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 920)
    - Thurston, Ann F. (National Committee on US-China Relations), 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 921)
    - Towle, Dr. and Mrs. Joseph W., 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 922)
    - Treudley, Mary B., 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 923)
    - Trotter, F. Thomas, 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 924)
    - Troxel, Mrs. Oliver L., 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 925)
    - Turk, Marsh, Kelly, Hoare, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 926)
    - Turner, John F., 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 927)
  - T - Taiwan
    - General
      - General file (Box 27, Folder 928)
      - Fu Jen Catholic University, 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 929)
      - St. John's and St. Mary's Institute of Technology c/o Taiwan Episcopal Church, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 930)
      - Taiwan First Investment (Box 27, Folder 930a)
    - Soochow University
      - General file (Box 27, Folder 931)
      - Chang, Pei-yang, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 932)
      - Denlinger, Paul B., 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 933)
      - Library (Box 27, Folder 934)
      - Music Department (Box 27, Folder 935)
      - Overseas personnel (Box 27, Folder 936)
      - Printed matter and publications, 1980-1991 (Box 27, Folder 937)
      - Proposals and grants, 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 938-942)
      - Twanmoh, Joseph K., 1980-1985 (Box 27, Folder 943)
      - Yang, Edward C. H., 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 944-945)
    - Tunghai University
      - General file (Box 28, Folder 946)
      - Alexander, Paul S., 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 947)
      - Alumni Association (Box 28, Folder 948)
      - Cha, Liang-Chien, 1980-1985 (Box 28, Folder 949)
      - Conferences, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 950)
      - Environment Project Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 951)
      - Fung, Hu-hsiang, 1980-1984 (Box 28, Folder 952)
      - Kiang, Yu-lung, 1980-1984 (Box 28, Folder 953)
      - Lin, Jun-yi, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 954)
      - Mei, Ko-wang, 1980-1987 (Box 28, Folder 955-956)
      - Overseas personnel (Box 28, Folder 957)
      - Pangilinan, Crispin, 1980-1984 (Box 28, Folder 958)
      - Proposals and grants, 1980-1986 (Box 28, Folder 959-964)
      - Rose, Juanelva, 1980-1989 (Box 28, Folder 965)
      - Scholarships, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 966-968)
      - Sun, Wesley K. C., 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 969)
  - T - Thailand
    - Payap University
      - General file (Box 28, Folder 970)
      - Christian Communications Institute, 1980-1986 (Box 28, Folder 971)
      - Kingshill, Konrad, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 972-973)
      - Library (Box 28, Folder 974)
      - Loan correspondence (of $50,000), 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 975)
      - Overseas personnel (Box 28, Folder 976)
      - Printed matter and publications, 1980-1990 (Box 28, Folder 977)
      - Proposals, grants, and reports, 1980-1987 (Box 28, Folder 978-984)
      - Tapingkae, Amnuay (Box 28, Folder 985)
  - U - General
    - U (Box 28, Folder 986)
    - Uerkuitz, Dr. and Mrs. David (Esther), 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 987)
    - Ulrich, Dr. and Mrs. Gene, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 988)
    - United Community Church, Wantagh, NY, 1980-1987 (Box 28, Folder 989)
    - United Ministries in Education, 1980-1987 (Box 28, Folder 990)
    - United States misc. A-Z (Box 28, Folder 991)
    - US: AID/ASHA lobby for Congressional funding, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 992)
    - US: AID/ASHA correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 29, Folder 993-994)
    - US: Department of Commerce, 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 995)
    - US: Internal Revenue Service, 1980-1987 (Box 29, Folder 996)
    - US: IRS challenge of UBCHEA housing allowance, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 997)
    - US: Department of the Treasury, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 998)
    - Univ (Box 29, Folder 999)
    - University A-L (Box 29, Folder 1000)
    - University M-Z (Box 29, Folder 1001)
    - University of East Asia, Macau, 1983-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1002)
    - University of Hawaii at Manoa, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1003)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1980-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1004)
    - University of Toronto, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1005)
  - V - General
    - V (Box 29, Folder 1006)
    - Van Vleck, Dr. and Mrs. Joseph (Louise), 1980-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1007)
    - Van Wyk, Gordon J., 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1008)
    - Villanueva, Virginia Laico (pianist), 1980-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1009)
    - Volunteers in Asia (Box 29, Folder 1010)
    - Vrooman, Julia Scott (estate of), 1980-1989 (Box 29, Folder 1011)
  - W - General
    - W (Box 29, Folder 1012)
    - Walls, Esther J. (Box 29, Folder 1013)
    - Wang, Dr. and Mrs. C. Herbert, 1980-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1014)
    - Wang, Mr. and Mrs. Ken Hsi, 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1015)
    - Washington DC Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1016)
    - Weatherford, Willis D. (Box 29, Folder 1017)
    - Webb, Christine, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1018)
    - Webb, H. Eugene, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1019)
    - Wei, Mark, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 1020)
    - Weidenhammer, Lillian, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 1021)
    - Welcher, Amy Ogden, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 1022)
    - Welcher, Emma A. (estate of), 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1023)
    - Weldy, Dr. and Mrs. Dwight (Marjorie), 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1024)
    - Wellesley College, Center for Women's Careers, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 1025-1026)
    - Wellesley College, Yenching Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1027)
    - Wells, Annie O. (estate of), 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 1028)
    - Wilcox, Dr. and Mrs. Glade (Minnie), 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 1029)
    - Wilson, Richard W., 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 1030)
    - Winfield, Dr. and Mrs. Gerald F. (Louise), 1980-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1031)
    - Wireman, Billy O., 1980-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1032-1033)
    - Women's Program, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1034)
    - World Council of Churches, Switzerland, 1981-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1035)
    - Wu Chung-I (Box 29, Folder 1036)
  - X - General
    - X (Box 29, Folder 1037)
  - Y - General
    - Y (Box 29, Folder 1038)
    - Yale University, general: A-Z (Box 29, Folder 1039)
    - Yale University Divinity School (Box 29, Folder 1040)
    - Young, David P., 1980-1989 (Box 29, Folder 1041)
    - Young, Herrick B., 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1042)
    - YMCA, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1043)
    - Yu, Timothy (Communications Development Consultant, Hong Kong), 1980-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1044)
    - Yuricic, Katherine, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1045)
  - Z - General
    - Z (Box 30, Folder 1046)
    - Zimmer, Ernst L., 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1047)
    - Zosa, Evangelina D., 1980-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1048)
- China Files, Series IV
  - A (Box 30, Folder 1049)
  - Agreement with Chinese Society for Education/ Ministry of Education, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 1350)
  - Agricultural Development Council (Box 39, Folder 1351)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1050)
  - Amity Foundation/ Hwa Nan -Lois Cole (Box 39, Folder 1352)
  - Amity Foundation/ Hwa Nan -Patricia McGill (Box 39, Folder 1353)
  - Amity Foundation/ Hwa Nan -Nancy Morgan (Box 39, Folder 1354)
  - Amity Foundation -Lynn Walter (Box 30, Folder 1051)
  - Amity Foundation: general correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 1052)
  - Amity Foundation: teachers, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1053)
  - Amity Foundation: NCCCUSA China Program, 1980-1989 (Box 30, Folder 1054)
  - Amity Foundation: former candidates and teachers, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1055)
  - Amity Foundation: former candidates and teachers, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 1056)
  - Amity Foundation: former candidates and teachers, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 1057)
  - Amity Foundation: former teachers, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1058)
  - Amity Foundation: general information, 1988-1991 (Box 30, Folder 1059)
  - Amity Foundation: general information, 1984-1990 (Box 30, Folder 1060)
  - Amity Foundation: history (Box 30, Folder 1061)
  - Anderson,. Bernard (Box 39, Folder 1355-1356)
  - Asia Society, 1982-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1062)
  - Ba - Bec (Box 30, Folder 1063)
  - Bed - Boo (Box 30, Folder 1064)
  - Beijing Foreign Affairs College, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 1065)
  - Beijing Foreign Affairs College, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1066)
  - Beijing Foreign Studies University - Books Library Project, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1067)
  - Beijing Teachers College (Capital Normal University) (Box 30, Folder 1068)
  - Board of Trustees China Tour, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 1357)
  - Board of Trustees Delegation to PRC (aborted), 1985 (Box 39, Folder 1358-1360)
  - Bullock, Mary Brown, 1980-1988 (Box 30, Folder 1069)
  - Butts, R. Freeman, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1070)
  - C (Box 30, Folder 1070a)
  - Center for US- China Arts Exchange, 1985-1990 (Box 30, Folder 1071)
  - Center for US - China Relations, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1072)
  - Central China University of Science and Technology, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1073)
  - China Connection, The, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1074)
  - China - former visiting professors, incl. Roger Johnson, Ruth Forney (Box 30, Folder 1075-1077)
  - China Programme -Canada, 1986-1994 (Box 31, Folder 1078)
  - China organizations - misc., 1982-1987 (Box 31, Folder 1079)
  - Chinese Academy of Science, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 1080)
  - Christianity in China - History, 1983-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1081)
  - Council on International Educational Exchange (CIEE), 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1082)
  - Cultural Center of the Philippines, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1083)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1084)
  - Former scholars from China - general, 1984-1988 (Box 31, Folder 1085-1087)
  - Former scholars: Chinese Educational Association for International Exchange, Jilin Provincial Branch, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 1088)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Chen - Gu (Box 31, Folder 1089-1092)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Hangchow Univ. - Hu (Box 31, Folder 1093-96)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Inner Mongolia Normal Univ. - Luo (Box 31, Folder 1097-1104)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Sichuan Conservatory of Music (Box 31, Folder 1105)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Wang - Wu (Box 31, Folder 1106-1112)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Xiang - Xu (Box 31, Folder 1113-1117)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Yan - Yu (Box 32, Folder 1118-1123)
  - Former scholars 1987-1993: Zhang - Zhu (Box 32, Folder 1124-1136)
  - Former scholars 1984-1987: general (Box 32, Folder 1137-1138)
  - Former scholars 1979-1987: Chang - Emory Univ. (Box 32, Folder 1139-1145)
  - Former scholars 1979-1987: Fujian Teachers Univ. - Huang (Box 32, Folder 1146-1152)
  - Former scholars 1979-1987: Li - Qian (Box 32, Folder 1153-1155)
  - H (Box 32, Folder 1156)
  - Hong Kong Baptist College: Library exchange program with university libraries in China (Mrs. Kitty T. K. Tse, Head Librarian), 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1157)
  - Hu, Xuzhi (Shzhi), Ministry of Education, Beijing (Box 32, Folder 1158)
  - Hua Chiao Univ. (Box 32, Folder 1159)
  - Hunter College: Grant for Social Anthropology Training Program hosted by Chinese Academy of Social Science, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 1160)
  - Hwa Nan Professional College for Women, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 1161)
  - I (Box 32, Folder 1162)
  - Institute: A-Z (Box 32, Folder 1163)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 32, Folder 1164)
  - International: A-Z (Box 32, Folder 1165)
  - International Association of Historians of Asia, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1166)
  - International Christian University at Shaanxi (Box 32, Folder 1167)
  - International Scientific Information Services, 1983-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1168)
  - J (Box 33, Folder 1169)
  - Ji, Humin (scholar attending Tufts University) (Box 33, Folder 1170)
  - Jiang, A-Z (Box 33, Folder 1171)
  - Jiang, Puqi (Cincinnati College - Conservatory of Music), 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 1172)
  - Jiang, Tao (Box 33, Folder 1173)
  - Jiangsu Teachers University (Box 33, Folder 1174)
  - Ka - Ke (Box 33, Folder 1175)
  - Kh - Ki (Box 33, Folder 1176)
  - Kl - Kz (Box 33, Folder 1177)
  - Kunming Teachers College (Box 33, Folder 1178)
  - Laney, James (Nanjing Colloquium) (Box 33, Folder 1179)
  - Lanzhou University, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1180)
  - La - Lee (Box 33, Folder 1181)
  - Lef - Lim (Box 33, Folder 1182)
  - Li: A-L (Box 33, Folder 1183)
  - Li, Guangzhao, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 1184)
  - Li: M-Z (Box 33, Folder 1185)
  - Li, Xia-Liang, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 1186)
  - Li, Yan, 1982-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1187)
  - Liang, Hubert S., 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1188)
  - Libraries, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1189)
  - Lin - Liz (Box 33, Folder 1190)
  - Lingnan University Memorial Association (Box 33, Folder 1191)
  - Liss, Norma D., 1980-1990 (Box 33, Folder 1192)
  - Liu: A-Z (Box 33, Folder 1193)
  - Liu, Chung-Jo (Sepal), 1985-1990 (Box 33, Folder 1194)
  - Liu, Xin-ru, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1195)
  - Lo - Lz (Box 33, Folder 1196)
  - Lu, Fan, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 1197)
  - Lui, Jin-han, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 1198)
  - Luo, Xian-hua, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1199)
  - Ma - Maz (Box 34, Folder 1200)
  - Madsen, Richard (Nanjing Colloquium) (Box 34, Folder 1201)
  - Maguire, John (Box 34, Folder 1202)
  - Mc: A-Z (Box 34, Folder 1203)
  - Me - Mi (Box 34, Folder 1204)
  - Mei, Shan OP 8 a,b,c Corr., 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1205)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. - Grant for China Programs, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 1206)
  - Michigan State University/ Sichuan, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 1207)
  - Midwest China Center, 1982-1987 (Box 34, Folder 1208)
  - Mo - Mz (Box 34, Folder 1209)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- "Education Towards Social Progress", 1988 Oct (Box 39, Folder 1361)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- correspondence with China, 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 1362)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- participants, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1363)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- interpreter, Kenneth Hao, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1364)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- Hayhoe paper, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1365)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- Lau paper, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1366)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- Phenix paper, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1367)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- Meng paper, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1368)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- Pan and Wu paper, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1369)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- Feng paper, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1370)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- miscellaneous papers, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1371)
  - Nanjing Colloquium- published volume of papers, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1372)
  - Nanjing University, 1982-1987 (Box 34, Folder 1210)
  - Nankai University, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1211)
  - National Committee on US/China Relations, 19897 (Box 34, Folder 1212)
  - Ne - Nog (Box 34, Folder 1213)
  - New York/ Beijing Friendship Committee (Box 34, Folder 1214)
  - Noh - Nz (Box 34, Folder 1215)
  - Northeast Teachers University, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1216)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association (Box 34, Folder 1217)
  - Oa - Old (Box 34, Folder 1218)
  - Ole - Ord (Box 34, Folder 1219)
  - Ore - Oz (Box 34, Folder 1220)
  - Pa (Box 34, Folder 1221)
  - Pe - Pog (Box 34, Folder 1222)
  - Poh - Pz (Box 34, Folder 1223)
  - Phenix, Philip (Nanjing Colloquium) (Box 34, Folder 1224)
  - Population Reference Bureau Inc. (Box 34, Folder 1225)
  - Presbyterian Church, Atlanta GA (Box 34, Folder 1226)
  - Princeton: China Christian College Archival Project (Box 34, Folder 1227)
  - Princeton: Summer Seminars in China Program (Box 34, Folder 1228)
  - Princeton University - general (Box 34, Folder 1229)
  - Princeton: Workshop of Comparative Cultures - Chinese, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1230)
  - Q (Box 34, Folder 1231)
  - Queensborough Community College: Scheller, Port of Entry (Box 35, Folder 1232)
  - Quisumbing, Agnes (for study to China) (Box 35, Folder 1233)
  - R (Box 35, Folder 1234)
  - Richardson, Edgar (Box 35, Folder 1235)
  - St. John's University, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1236)
  - Se - Shan (Box 35, Folder 1237)
  - Shaanxi Teachers University: Library Project, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 1238)
  - Shaanxi Teachers University, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 1239)
  - Shaanxi Teachers University, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 1240)
  - Shaanxi Teachers University, 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 1241)
  - Shaanxi Teachers University: consultancy, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1242)
  - Shaanxi Teachers University: equipment, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 1243-1245)
  - Shaanxi: Teachers University: books (Box 35, Folder 1246)
  - Shaanxi: Teachers University: Library Trainee correspondence, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1247)
  - Shaanxi: Teachers College Periodicals, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1248)
  - Shaanxi: Teachers University Workshops (Box 35, Folder 1249)
  - Shaanxi: Teachers University Teams (Box 35, Folder 1250)
  - Shao, Ru-Chen (Box 35, Folder 1251)
  - Sheldon, Mark, 1980-1990 (Box 35, Folder 1252)
  - Shen, Grace Sung-wei, 1984-1991 (Box 35, Folder 1253)
  - Shen, Huihui, 1980-1984 (Box 35, Folder 1254)
  - Shen, Qi, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1255)
  - Sichuan: Library Equipment, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1256)
  - Sichuan: Institute of Finance and Economy (Box 35, Folder 1257)
  - Sichuan University: Consultancy, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1258)
  - Sichuan University: Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 1259)
  - Sichuan University: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1260)
  - Sichuan University: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 1261)
  - Sichuan University: Equipment, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1262)
  - Sichuan University: Librarian Trainees (Box 36, Folder 1263-1267)
  - Sichuan University: Teams, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1268)
  - Sichuan University: Books, corres., 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1269)
  - Sichuan University: Books, Baker Taylor Co., Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 1270)
  - Sichuan University: Workshops (Box 36, Folder 1271)
  - Simmons College, US and Wuhan University, PRC, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1272)
  - Sophia University, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 1273)
  - South China Normal University, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1274)
  - South-West Teachers College, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1275)
  - Sta - Stu (Box 36, Folder 1276)
  - Stanford University/ East China Normal (Box 36, Folder 1277)
  - Stanford University, CA; Thomas Fingar (Box 36, Folder 1278)
  - State Education Commission Provincial Level: Jiangsu (Box 36, Folder 1279)
  - State Education Commission Provincial Level: Jianxi (Box 36, Folder 1280)
  - State Education Commission Provincial Level: Shandong (Box 36, Folder 1281)
  - State Education Commission Provincial Level: Shanghai (Box 36, Folder 1282)
  - Str - Sz (Box 36, Folder 1283)
  - Sun, Margaret, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 1350)
  - Suzhou (Soochow) University: Taiwan, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1284)
  - Suzhou University, Suzhou, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1285)
  - Th (Box 36, Folder 1286)
  - Ti - To (Box 36, Folder 1287)
  - Tianjin Foreign Studies Institute, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 1288)
  - Ting, Bishop K. H., President, China Christian Council, Nanjing Theological Seminary, PRC (Box 37, Folder 1289)
  - Ting, Stephen Yen Ren, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 1290)
  - Tr - Tz (Box 37, Folder 1291)
  - US/ China Exhange: Center, Columbia Univ. School of Arts, Dir. Prof. Chou Wen-Chung (Box 37, Folder 1292)